<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Akshay Easwaran</title>
    <description>Sports Fan, Student, Developer</description>
    <link>http://akeaswaran.me</link>
    <atom:link href="http://akeaswaran.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Kicking and Screaming</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/will-ferrell-ks.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Will Ferrell in Kicking and Screaming (photo via
  http://www.sky.com/tv/movie/kicking-and-screaming-2005)&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;small&quot; style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Will Ferrell in &lt;i&gt;Kicking and Screaming&lt;/i&gt; (photo via
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sky.com/tv/movie/kicking-and-screaming-2005&quot;&gt;Sky&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://akeaswaran.me/kicking-and-screaming/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://akeaswaran.me/kicking-and-screaming/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yellow Jackets in the NFL</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;With Week 1 of the 2016 NFL season in the books, I take a look at how last year’s draft class of Yellow Jackets is adjusting to life in the NFL.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://akeaswaran.me/projackets-2016/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://akeaswaran.me/projackets-2016/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Birth of the 1996 Atlanta Olympic Games</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;display:block;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/olympic-cauldron.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;https://www.olympic.org/photos/aaaey013&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://akeaswaran.me/1996-atlanta-olympics/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://akeaswaran.me/1996-atlanta-olympics/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Beginning of the End</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;display:block;margin-left:auto;margin-right:auto;&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/ted-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Turner Field&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://akeaswaran.me/the-ted/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://akeaswaran.me/the-ted/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So Long and Thanks for All the Fish, Megatron</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Calvin Johnson is one of football’s most dynamic playmakers. In his nine years in
“the League”, he’s dazzled opposing defenses with his quick feet and great
hands, positioning himself in the discussion for greatest wide receiver to ever
play the game, alongside Hall of Famers like Lynn Swann, Jerry Rice, and Michael
Irvin. Every week, regardless of how his team, the Detroit Lions, was doing on
the season, he came out and competed, even during the doldrums of the Lions’
0-16 season in 2008. But one of football’s biggest stars had his humble
beginnings in the Atlanta area and rose to stardom under the same lights Justin
Thomas and Marcus Marshall do today.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://akeaswaran.me/megatron-retires/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://akeaswaran.me/megatron-retires/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>One Last Ride for the Sheriff? (Super Bowl 50 Preview)</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Super Bowl 50 (No, not Roman numeral L, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cbssports.com/nfl/eye-on-football/25464168/super-bowl-l-is-for-losers-but-nfl-will-return-to-roman-numerals-after-50&quot;&gt;for obvious
reasons&lt;/a&gt;)
will be played between the Carolina Panthers and the Denver Broncos at Levi’s
Stadium in Santa Clara, CA on February 7, 2016. Now that we’re through with the
cursory details, here’s my preview of the “Big Game”.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://akeaswaran.me/super-bowl-50-preview/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://akeaswaran.me/super-bowl-50-preview/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Win Big, Storm the Field</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve always been a huge football fan. Now, I’ve never played a down of the sport, but I’ve lived and breathed it for as long as I can remember. One of my earliest memories is of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/5g2evJ0BRvs?t=18m36s&quot;&gt;final play of Super Bowl XXXIV&lt;/a&gt;; I was 2-years-old and awed by a navy-shirted man who dove for a big white line as a white-shirted man grabbed for his ankles. Ever since then, I’ve been hooked to the sport, watching every game I can and learning as much about its deep and rich history as possible. I used to be a huge bandwagon fan; I grew up in an era where my hometown team (the San Francisco 49ers) was middling at best and Brett Favre, Peyton Manning, and Tom Brady ruled the skies, the scoreboards, and the record books; so naturally, I was drawn to the teams that won the most: the Packers, Colts, and Patriots of the NFL. Watching these teams play instilled me with a love of the game and a love of victory that remains to this day.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://akeaswaran.me/miracle-on-techwood-drive/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://akeaswaran.me/miracle-on-techwood-drive/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alternate Realities</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;For 2016, one of my New Year’s Resolutions is to get off my lazy behind and do something productive with my free time. I have a few hobbies that I want to develop as I get older, the foremost being my writing. That brings me here to Medium. My goal is to write a short-form article every week about something that interests me. Maybe this will last a while, and maybe it won’t; either way, it doesn’t hurt to try.
So, in the first of what I hope to be many entries, let’s talk about alternate realities.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://akeaswaran.me/alt-realities/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://akeaswaran.me/alt-realities/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>